const harryPotter =
[
	{
  "id": 1,
  "question": "What are the names of Harry's parents",
  "answers": ["James and Lily Potter", "Luna and Neville Potter", "Marge and Lupin Potter"],
  "correctAnswer": "James and Lily Potter"
	}, 

	{
  "id": 2,
  "question": "Who did Harry live with in muggle world",
  "answers": ["Malfoys", "Dursleys", "Grangers"],
  "correctAnswer": "Dursleys"
	}, 

	{
  "id": 3,
  "question": "What clothing article sorts wizards and witches into houses",
  "answers": ["scarf", "boots", "hat"],
  "correctAnswer": "hat"
	}, 
	
  {
  "id": 4,
  "question": "What animal can Harry Speak to",
  "answers": ["snake", "wolf", "rat"],
  "correctAnswer": "snake"
	},
  
  {
  "id": 5,
  "question": "who brought harry to the Dursleys",
  "answers": ["Hagrid", "Dumbledore", "Tonks"],
  "correctAnswer": "Hagrid"
	},
  
  {
  "id": 6,
  "question": "What animal can Harry Speak to",
  "answers": ["snake", "wolf", "rat"],
  "correctAnswer": "snake"
	},
  {
  "id": 7,
  "question": "What position in Quidditch did Harry play?",
  "answers": ["seeker", "beater", "keeper"],
  "correctAnswer": "seeker"
	},
 
  {
  "id": 8,
  "question": "Where is the secret meeting place for DumbleDore's Army?",
  "answers": ["great hall", "Room of Requirement", "Gryffindor Commons"],
  "correctAnswer": "Room of Requirement"
	},
  
  {
  "id": 9,
  "question": "What do you recite to close the Marauder's Map?",
  "answers": ["Lumos", "Got them good", "Mischief Managed"],
  "correctAnswer": "Mischief Managed"
	},
  
  {
  "id": 10,
  "question": "What is Harry's patronus?",
  "answers": ["dog", "snake", "stag"],
  "correctAnswer": "stag"
	},
  
  {
  "id": 11,
  "question": "What substance is strong enough to destroy a horcrux?",
  "answers": ["Spell", "thor's Hammer", "Basilisk venom"],
  "correctAnswer": "Basilisk venom"
	},
  
  {
  "id": 12,
  "question": "What magical device did Albus Dumbledore use to save and review his memories",
  "answers": ["a phenoix", "Pensieve", "PortKey"],
  "correctAnswer": "Pensieve"
	}
]




module.exports = {harryPotter}; 